Lights flicker, mics hum, psyche hits go live
And here they are, come on, gotta beat a preachin' truth
With a cat on her lap, ghost drops a hundred
Just to start up the clap, Tony's flexin'
Big Pops rantin' and rhyme, pay starts a sermon
It's confession time
Laughing like the queen of sin
God he's spinning tales with a devilish grin
Alexandra once ridd my soul like glass
Now I toast a ghost with a whiskey pass
Fawzi qu-
to the wild ones, broken and bright
the avatars dancing through
the night, the trolls, the poets, the saints
the insane, all baptized
in the live stream rain
it's the open panel circus baby, amen
the show goes on
just not with them
I was caught inside the storm of my own fear
Lightening struck and words fell sharp and clear
Didn't mean to let the thunder roll your name
I was reaching for connection not to lay the blame
You were the calm in my wild parade
I was afraid, and though I stumbled through the noise inside my head, I never spoke your name in anger, only in regret.
So thank you, Alexandra, for all you-
For the mirror you held when I couldn't see through
No bitterness no mask to defend
Just love that linger
my closet, if I win and I prove you wrong, you give 50 to me and 50 to Jimny. 50 to me and 50 to Jimny.
I'm not agreeing to shoot. Yeah, yeah. Because my fucking kid is fucking organized. I have OCD 4.
I am a horse. Yeah. So, actually, it's colorized. It's like, I have my sweater. It's folded up. Everything is in perfect position. Yes or no, I don't give a fuck. I like you. I like you. Oh, you want to see my closet? You want to see my closet? Oh, okay. You want to come on me again? Huh? Oh, I definitely will come on you.
What you will never get a chance to come near me. You just have been said to you say you
Come at me. You understand English. Come on. You said come on. I said come on
Shut the fuck up. Hey attention to Jimmy. Oh, I like that. That's a cute rose hoodie
It's like I have my sweater. It's folded up. Everything is perfect. Yes. No, I don't I like you
Oh, I definitely will come on you
What?
You will never get a chance to come near me. You just have this
It's like I have my sweater. It's folded up
i'm in the show i'm in the show i'm in the show
see psych how thing that is is laughing in the chat
a riser is big tall sexy rob that's a freebie i know things my little white hair friend
You gotta fix your mic man. You should be the loudest one on the panel. Not me
I love you songs
Yes
no you've been very low lately I think you've been doing it on purpose
think that is actually tried to tell you earlier but it's still maintained low
I don't know why that fucking wig freaked me out last night bro
you took in my surprise with that shit and it like sparks some kind of childhood trauma or something
oh I don't want to do that okay no no no I love it now I love it how do you love it
yeah
the
still pretty low man
I know, you shouldn't be able to see it though, okay?
There you go.
So, yeah, I didn't mean to like come off as,
I don't know, now it's like, you know,
and everyone's sort of saying the same thing about like,
she's like, oh yeah, I know what people are talking about
now with you, and that's like what everyone says
like when they like, so maybe I do,
I guess I have personality flaws.
I do talk too much on the show,
and I know that bothers people.
I think she wanted more of like a no contact
like me not addressed to her.
I mean I might, you know
Who are we talking about gene don't number one or two?
One is be there two is Alex
Okay, number two number two. Okay. Yeah, but you know what I don't want to put them in like
There's not an order or anything cuz now she's doing now. She's saying like
I mean, I did watch her show tonight and she's like, well, she's like, I'm she thinks I'm like not gay
I'm like bisexual and that you know, I have misrepresented myself
What the hell is that any business of hers? Who cares about that? Why is that even coming into the picture?
And I didn't and she doesn't misrepresent myself and I was like I don't feel like I did like that
Because I all I ever said was I'd like the friendship
You know, it's like you know, and I was not it's like well
I actually said that to you because sometimes you don't act gay like I forget you're gay because you act so cool and like
You can be like both you can act gay when you want or be like not gay-ish when you want
But that doesn't matter in anything at all actually in whatever's going on. That shouldn't even be a variable
Now I look now I've ended up looking like that
The glasses the hair those fucking beard
can't really hear me, I can like, fix my microphone hole
No, I hear you better man, it's not perfect, I'm sure, I'm screaming through my...
Wait, is it on right? Let me see, okay, so...
Yeah, yeah, you sound louder
Not even, okay, so better
Let me lower mine
Is that better? Is that better? It might be a little bit better
Yes, okay, it's better. You've been like muffled for the past three days like in the background like we can hear you
But it hasn't been like, you know my default microphone will now be the
Yeah, you got to go to default to hit a speaker phone microphone. I put it all back on board
And I can't take it high definition audio device. I mean there's so many options. Okay, so this is fine
There we go, it was halfway down. Okay, perfect. Okay
Do I sound better now?
Yes, you sound louder than me. Perfect.
It's a bit better? Okay. Sorry.
You're gonna give me a trouble. I don't want to get yeah, and like please like you know guys like no mind control
Round a people on my show
It's like hard enough keeping track of like what actual people are doing rather than like you know because I mean it's like
Stop it. I know it's it. I mean it's like I totally do believe in it
It's up and uh, please just stop knowing what so I'm not trying to mind control me, too
But feel you're trying to get inside my brain
of the
Tell me she's crazy bro. I think that is
Now she's saying I'm asking people to attack her. No, I don't I don't please do not like she is a sweet sweet like kind lady
And it's like, you know, she I have nothing bad to say about her
She's awesome and I would she thinks I'm like some henchmen of beta or something. I guess she thinks
Henchmen of beta
So we she went from loving you
to visiting you taking you out making panels of you promoting you in a month and now
You're a henchman of beta. Oh, what the fuck did I miss?
She thinks all the bend beta likes my death or something she said and then um, I'll read you to her post
No, but what happened? What happened? What was the turning point?
I look away for one day come back. You're a henchman of beta
That's why I'm like, and also it's happening with other people too, like people getting mad at me, so I was like, I don't know, oh, oh, oh, oh.
That's funny. That's hilarious. That's why I say don't trust nobody. I can't
You know, yo your first friend flag should have been when she started doxing beta
When stag ladies started making panels using beta's name. No, no, I don't pay listen for one second
Okay, I know she's your friend and you're neutral and you love both of them, but
bro that was not cool at all okay that that come on that's a reflect bro
that's super doxing
picture i made panels of you with your full name as the title every day and bad talking about you
like that's super doxing to the max and polis and that's not cool so she acts so in like innocent
I didn't want to talk, okay, that was good to send out, but you don't really like what's supposed to be the topic of discussion.
I just want to say, I think to myself, I'm going to play this song again.
I should sing to this song. I'll play it. There's another version of something.
Okay, but I really do a lot.
It's a pretty song.
Ugh, I feel this dumb. I'm sorry. I should not.
I think she said boundaries, and so I was like, and I know I can like, you know, I just say,
if I think it's just like any boundaries, I apologize, I try to be respectful, and they're
going to try that.
And I don't know, like she said, be just kind of mastermind, you know, I don't, I don't
think be the, I mean, it's like, there really don't think be just like that favorite
See like beating it's like a lot of respects like I could just like I don't get any respect like I've had like I've asked people like
Start talking about me on like beat is urban or about me on the panels with people and
It's like you beat it
To be like how's talking about me and like
Then it's like they're fine talking on panels about me and then it was to get by bring up anything
They're like, oh, we don't talk about that. We don't talk about that. We don't talk about that
So it's like, okay, well really it's like well if you have no problem talking about another shows like why do you have a problem?
Okay, I'm not going to take this, I don't know if you guys understand that.
Hey, Joni, all your trolls are on the, I don't know, I mean, it's like, I think they just, like, follow me, like, me and, like, us around because it's, like, I really see, like, they probably, like, just know always when you're live, so, I don't know.
Why is she, she's mad, because I, well, maybe because I, I did, like, you know,
They kind of like mentioned to everybody that, you know, she said, like, she wanted to take a 30 day break and then we kind of got, I didn't get to fight with her in her chat, but it was just kind of, we had a weird conversation where I was like, well, I want to talk to you private.
And she's like, and she's like, no, I don't want to talk to you private.
But she told me to like, stop harassing Carl in the room.
So I just like left.
And then I like, maybe like went on a bit to do a little bit about it, but I don't.
I don't know, but it's fine, it's fine, I mean, but she's saying like, kind of like, I mean, it's fine, she can say whatever she wants about me, you know, it's like, I just just like, careful with, I just say, I feel like I'm being lumped in with like a lot of things, and like just really having certain people,
I just like, you know, just, I like, weren't, weren't anybody about putting jackets on people because it's like not
necessarily easy life, sometimes for people that are like, you know, just like slandered like that, yeah.
Like I'm not saying anybody in particular, or anybody slandered or anything, but I've seen, I've seen a lot of like,
Because it's like a bit, because we already have everyone being accused of something, right?
That is like, we accused the first thing, that is like, it's like, it's hierarchical, like accusations, like it was the most accusatory thing to do, it's crazy, you know?
And it's okay, but I just think, I have a show and it's like, I kind of like hope people know, like, if you're gonna like, you know, probably, if you're a friend, especially if you're another content creator, and we like meet and stuff like that, you know, it's like, I mean, I don't really...
And I hope that after the 30 days they will talk to me and I can talk to them, but I don't feel like I've even been to talk to Pita for something like a week at all, or then I have to see Pita in her job.
I was with Bob, but she said she thinks I'm extremely in love with Pita and I know I'm like a weird person where it's like, you know, Emma and Pita.
at least since we're Donna you know like different like women I like talk to or whatever then like
most of them end up you know most of those people do not like but you guys still hear me I'm sorry
but um or it's like or never did or I don't know it's like it was funny because that the woman
Yeah, it's like thank you angels. I think I have a crystal and DJ Electra and
Page like occasionally, but it's like, you know, they're all like, you know off the set it's like a cigarette somewhere
Did you see some of the boy that she's pulling my six it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
It's okay. I'm here in a wig like, you know, and I still like basketball. I'm probably I still look like
Like the elf king or something. It's okay
No, I can take it. I can take it. I don't want to say anything major. I really don't and it's like I feel it's been miscontrude already
I think really people are going back and they're trying to cause conflict forced saying I'm so always saying this or they're flipping things
I'd like to complete. I'm not trying to send people to her. I want to help the rotor of they still do but it's like I think that
Uh, it's just sad, it's like another one, it's like another, I feel like I just like get kind of like just dumped.
Sometimes like, you know, like Emily never talked to me, you know, like, you know, and you have like this past life feeling with some people and maybe that's why it's like, I go into things like weird...
Like that's really obsessive like it's not like we're obsessive, but it's just like you know
I got I get things like ideas in my head or like to memories
Some some people and like or even I don't know and it's just like
It's not like like plus full is just like you know, nostalgia. It's like
It's like, you know
It's really not sense. It's not sexual, but then it's like I've done it again. It's like I did have like
I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what, I'm not saying who or what
You know, but I don't enjoy being treated like garbage. And I wasn't I really was not abused by anybody my childhood
You know, you know, I understand like I really was more used by people later
So but I understand like there are I do sometimes like
She said, my pattern is like burning towards people,
or they're trying to push people that love and care about me.
And then like chasing after people that hate me
and should be like garbage.
And it's like, that's just,
that's the thing for me to think about as a character flaw.
But I feel like I'm really not like chasing anybody around
at this point.
Like I let things kind of come to me and I don't like
force myself in people's lives to try not to see me.
So, and I'm just like not very good socially.
And so,
I'm sure I did something wrong or I shouldn't be talking this much, but it's okay, whatever she thinks or whatever, it's her perception, and she's right to it, and she's a strong independent woman, and I love that about her, I'm never going to falter for anything she thinks, feels, and it's like, really just doesn't like me, it's fine.
I didn't mean for anything to get all messed up, like, you know, I just, it just seems like it's like,
I feel like it's a gastrological because just,
like, it happens with a few people.
I just got really mad.
That's why I'm going, I must be doing something.
anything to say you're included what is it oh the 30 days she said in 30 days she
said oh well I said an email three nights ago she said oh well I'm not
I'm I'm taking a 30 day break and I was like okay then I think later that's
I should let you clarify there was like 30 breaks and switch off my channel except
I picked the channel
But I could sort of hear what she said, and then I was talking in her chat, and Carl was
in there, and he started calling me a big boy in the chat, and I was like, I called him an old man.
So then she told me to calm down, and I was like...
acting like Gels and Carl because they went with the beat or something.
And I was just like, oh my gosh, and then I just like left, and then that's all I said.
And I'm not saying anything beside it, just what happened.
Like I'm not trying to say anything negative or teaser or anything.
I really, I really, really like real kids, so we'll be friends under the 13th or whatever.
You know, but it's like, they just won't, I'm not lying, I'm like, I'll tell the whole
She never really said a negative thing to me until like, just like, just like, you know, until this is so I don't know if like, yeah.
Oh, the ear hook, mate. Okay, I'm sorry. I'm sorry for missing the chat.
Yeah.
Look, look, you know, someone's talking about autism, you know, it's like...
I think everybody like has like it's a human mind if they we have like these little things
because we have these different sort of work we have things for whatever thing but those are just
like kind of like taking a bunch of symptoms and like putting them into a thing it's like we all
have like a lot of things but there's a lot of things especially what we bring out of your mind
and it's like and I've done a lot of like but we'll basically say like a lot of
Self-discovery exploit that's why I was trying to tell her about like a little thing
Okay, so it's like kind of a complicated, but you know, like a little there's a certain type of woman that is like really exemplified
Okay, and like and I'm a little biotin is one. I think at least it's or Donna is one
but also
This is her big pipes to this reading like you know on like what kind of demon would Alex be and I said
Lilith and it's like so I think that she has that energy too
you know and like other women think that I've known and it's like but uh yeah so this little energy
and but it's like but I have like this cast like memories about Lilith and like just knowing
we're like a lot of lifetimes and like I know her it's like she's like red hair like freckled
So she's like, Nita's my love.
And I said, Nita's my love.
They look like my love is for people at all.
Like, Nita might be like, you know, my Taurus.
But Taurus might be like, I don't know if it's like,
she does, they change, but she's always dark and stuff.
She likes, you know, like dark and stuff.
Like, so inside of the hat, like, she doesn't want to be
out projected out to like other people.
She doesn't, that's what she,
and she unfortunately, she'll possess them and get like,
I don't know what it is, I don't know what it is, I don't know what it is, I don't know
I'm probably not very socially intelligent, so I don't know, I would say you could call it even possible, but it's just different.
It's very, very trusting, but at the same time, I've been okay mainly.
So it's like I haven't really trusted somebody that brought me into too much physical danger.
They go in their shopping, it is really a while to go.
I feel like I was kind of getting into judges with theirs.
Anyway, yeah, that week just saw me.
How much time has it been?
11, yeah.
Yeah, I mean, it's like, I hope, I hope that whatever it is, I hope, I just wish it was like, I'm sorry if I said something wrong.
I didn't mean to like, I'm not trying to like, she was like, she, like I'll read you her post and it's like, her post was like...
I was kind of like, what, I just didn't understand really what she's talking about, but if anyone wants to translate it to me, you can, um, hold on, so, okay, but then she posted another thing, like, okay, so she posted on her board.
For those who have continued to ask me about why I've chosen to essentially go no contact
with Psyche Awakens, the answer is 0.3 within this video, so there's a video there.
And he says, I haven't seen it, okay?
I was like, I kind of heard that she was talking about me, so I was like, that's too
far off.
But he says, I'm very aware of who he's egging on to trash talk me on his panel.
No surprise, he's very passive-aggressive, and I'm aware of the false narratives being pushed about me.
Bottom line, I'm not okay with teen groomers of febophiles, pedophiles, and or child abusers,
and that's something public figures' beta enables and condones, along with a few other criminal elements.
Psyche misrepresented his situation to me. I don't hate him, but I'm not interested in being a part of anything revolving around
I do wish he'd respect my boundaries, but truth be told
He's incapable of being solid when it comes to someone like myself at the stage of his life
Trying to force someone like me to be okay with evil is wrong
God will take care of the situation. I removed myself from that social group was the right thing to do
And then but then later she posted again
She said
Our friends at psyche awakens did he reveal the truth of that thing that is tonight. Good job. I
Mean it wasn't too bad. I mean it's like wasn't like
We all have a little troll-blit in this.
I think that's the thing, is that we all have that side and maybe it comes out with certain
people that trigger us in a certain way, I don't know.
I was trying to be fair and balanced with the interview.
I'm happy to help people promote as much as they want to.
People are welcome on the panel, people are welcome to promote their shows.
Even if you even and then she was like saying like oh, she's like I let up Sam man and he's like I
Mean someone came in the chat today saying oh my god
Well, Sam man plays Roblox or something and then these and then because he plays Roblox
He was accusing him of the PTF and it's like
That to me is just like things going too far
Kind of ridiculous
Time the smile
How far up is the, let's see if it's time.
Yeah, here it is.
Thank you, will you please admit, I'm not gay,
and I am in love with PETA.
Thing that is, is a warlock energy vampire.
PETA is a Mexican gang leader trying to
alien Alexandra.
It seems very rational.
You know what? I think that might be like the truth though, I mean all that what you said, I think that's just like the simplest explanation basically based on like, I mean, how it works, this is like what makes most sense to me.
I mean, it doesn't it to you? Because, well, except for me, I'm not gay, like I do love Vita, I mean, I say I do, but I'm not in love, but I love so I can say, and I'm not, no, I'm not like happy.
Sometimes so maybe I don't know I did date a woman once for a few months, but it was not it was like a it was like a read
I don't know I have to be like talking to a made manipulated and I need to be groomed into a straight relationship
Okay, I need some serious grooming including like you know the gourmet like they're really like you know the fancy expensive dog food
So it's what's with all the weird stuff around the edges are you talking about my uh, this
Cat, let me see, so I'm overthinking, okay.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's like Occam's razor just cut away
which doesn't make sense.
So it's, yeah, the simplest thing, yeah,
because well it's like,
Gear hood, the Gear hood, okay, I'll look it up.
On Amazon, okay.
Yeah.
She.
Who is she?
I just feel like it's something
that they can't do anything right, so you know what?
I just, like, I feel like, I feel like I wanted to, like, you know, talk, like, just, like,
talk to her, like, or something about it, and it's like, I think I can only talk to her
in her chat right now.
It's like, it was Vita, right?
It's like, I don't know.
It's Vita.
I had to have Vita's number.
I had to have the number.
That's like, I'm not going to follow them on my phone.
It's like, it's like, oh my god, that's okay.
It's the first thing.
Not like they would say this, but like, you know.
Oh wait, is it key to call my phone one or two times?
It's like, see, like, first thing.
I just don't want to bother people in their show, you know, honestly, but I feel like I kind of can be a distraction.
If I'm in the show, somebody's show, like sometimes unless they like want me to, you know, talk, so then I'll like look around.
But you know I and I don't like the thing is like Sam and it's like annoying as fuck and like he does like
Hey, I'm here right now, and it's like I really like I should yeah, I should be like
Oh, F them and like, you know, and I told her and I told her and she also told me like I don't mean to disclose too much
But she said, you know, oh, she's like I understand if you ever want to talk to me to give me friends with her
I you know, I understand because she always knew she always was like, oh, you know
You really care for you or that and it was like but it turned into like now like I'm obsessed with her
And like, you know, I'm like I'm like in competition with call now. It's like, okay
I'm like in a competition with like with like Carl and think that is I think it's like, you know
Well, they could probably like, I don't know, they could probably like, you know, figure out some kind of like,
nerdy weapon or something, but I could do real magic, right? But they can too, probably. I mean, I don't know.
I remember Bita said Carl Kirstner and then her life was number the same. That's all I remember, but if she told me that on the phone, I don't want to gossip or shit about what I'm saying to her, she doesn't.
But, maybe...
Is it possible that like I don't know because I believe in this metaphysical stuff, and I believe in the spiritual war too
so is it possible
that
She wants to like lift the curse and so she's like that's why she's nice to call
She wants him to like you know, or do the he wants
or she wants to do like a counter ceremony or like
Do you think she wants it back like all these kind of interesting questions, right?
because
I can tell there's like a lot of emotions around her crying over me. It just seemed like it was like a little bit
Like if I'm up here right now, I think it was a little bit
Over it was like it was like basically a way for her to get like a lot of sympathy, you know, because
What's the twist in the car? I'll be just sorry. I don't know
I've been out of the loop a little bit because I have a memory. Well, yeah, there's been like folks
I'm using that thing.
What's the twist and twist in the Carl and Rita story, what?
Not to discuss it, but it's interesting, though.
Oh, yeah, it is interesting.
Yeah, we can discuss Carl and Rita.
I don't care, it's like because they're, you know, she has a show.
I can discuss people with shows.
It's like that's why we're here. It's like to be talked about and to talk about the people
I mean, that's kind of what being a radio or I don't know what YouTube post is
It's like especially for me because I'm a like a live streamer with open panels. So I
Don't know I
Kind of have to do like all this stuff myself, you know, so I really a lot myself and it's like, you know with a very very low budget and
Anyway, I have some new shorts coming, not the actual shorts, I should be signing some more stuff, but I should be posting new shorts.
Come in soon.
Okay, someone came up.
Hello.
Hello, hello, how are you?
Okay, how are you doing?
I'm okay. So yeah, just to kind of let you know what's happening. It's not really discussing
Beat us. So I hope she doesn't get upset about this. It's just what's going on
Thing that is that's where your mom won't come to your room today dick and you tried to hide her
You got up. Yeah, you live with your mom dick. I do you an established man. I'm one of my ex military
You're just 90 years. How old are you? How old do you live in the mommy's house? I'm 58 and I
In your mind dreams of after you
Your mom came in today to take your little coffee cup away. I call it. I'm always watching digesty
I'm always watching you my mother needed and you were hard dropped
When my mother told me no, I got rid of my condo and let my mother move in with me
And now my uncle is going through dementia and he needs people to take care of him. So he now lives here, too
So you're good. If you think that makes me a loser or something like that
I don't give a crap man. I mean
I just saw when she came in and you try to hide or you got open like put the shoulder and I hit the cam
I'm like why is he ashamed of his mom?
He should be coming her up like say hi to my mom
That's exactly why I don't want her to be on camera, man. That's that's why I was upset
That's why I was like don't just come in man like nox. So I know to turn the camera off
correct
Your mom's on the bus you see how crazy I am bro. I'll attack anything I see man. I'm always watching
But I'm also
No, I've been on my own since I was like
20 21 maybe around that was on my own and then around
4950 like I just whatever life was
Being what you know, it's my mom. We're gonna take care of our parents in their old age because they care about the whole life
And that's the game they take care of us and then at the end we take care of them
I come from that, you know, Greek old school tradition thing, right where you know, just cast the
Correct the old-timers up right you never I would never put my parents in a nursing home never they'll die next to me
My living room like what are you crazy? That's what it is. That's some crazy shit
It's just so it's in a nursing home
Circumstances have led to this point. So we all got together and we got this
This town home together in my mind
My uncle needs constant help. I mean he's getting to the point where we're getting so you got your mom and her brother
Wander away now what?
So you're taking care of your mom and her brother. I mean, I'm helping my mother around
I'm helping her out. I wouldn't say I'm taking care of her
She's really taking care of my uncle and I'm just kind of like helping out. That's why I'm usually
Marvels, she's not old. No, he's not old. Yeah, that's why I'm usually up at night
So I can give let my mom have the day to herself, you know, I'm not in her way and all that stuff
You know, and I work from home. So it's not like I have to be up at a certain hour
To be at an office. So I envy you man having your family close to you
Yeah, I think that's why I go so order people cuz you know, and I know how it is on the internet
I mean once people find that stuff out, it's it becomes a joke and it's like, okay
Well, I mean, I'm not embarrassed to be taking care of my mother and her, you know elderly age
You know, it's just the way it is. No, I'm gonna be ashamed though. Yeah
Especially my uncle man, like he's really he's in pretty bad shape
Yeah, I come from Colombia man and there that shit doesn't exist nursing homes don't exist there, right?
Yeah, your parents live with you to you know, like the family lives together like
United States is a whole different like mindset
There are other countries that's all about family like not living with your parents is like crazy
Right here. It's like oh, I gotta die like be alone
Getting crazy
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
You know in psyches panel instead of you what j-dog or beta or alexandra mayor says or even me or a thing
That's the problem. You know what psych you would have been a 10k by now, bro
But every day you wasted on your all your energy on all these other people. It's just like a
psych or a ballroom door
You're a pretty good position to talk to beta
Cuz I know she was very upset about J-Dog, especially and Alexander and if both of them have abandoned you then
Honestly, I have no place in any of this. I don't know J-Dog beater or you guys you guys have been family like forever
I'm just a dick up here talking shit
But Alex, I was going to say, where are countries, if you look at like India, they've got like four generations living in one house, huh?
Yeah, exactly.
Like it should be.
That's family, man. I don't know what the hell's going on over here, bro.
The calm in my wild parade
The friend that never flinched when I was afraid
I was coming up here psyched by you about the latest Karlo Vita twist
So this doesn't really involve them directly, the third party
So thank you, Alexandra, for all you gave
For the laughter, the light, the way you stand
You gotta stop making songs of these stupid girls, Dick.
It's been like three months already.
I like saying you beat us songs every day, Dick, and get your head back in the game,
asshole.
They warned me I might lose what I adore.
Told them leave her be, she's finding her own home
I never turn, I never let it twist
Just pray for peace in the space we meet
true for the mirror you held when I couldn't see through no bitterness no
mass to defend just love that lingers and adore
you there okay so let me just really quickly let me just tell you i got censored
babe i wonder what i said anyways um so carls x contacted betta one day to talk behind the scenes
okay and then she appeared
on a few of Beedah's panels.
At this point, we didn't know that she was Carl Zach's
or that Carl was involved in any way.
You never care about something or other, right?
Mimi, you remember Mimi, right?
She didn't talk much when she was on Beedah's panels.
Then all of a sudden, a few days ago,
she appears with Carl on yours, I think it was, right?
She was on Alexander's.
Was it Alexandra's, who's ever, whoever it was, she appears, they appear together on
and she's calling Bita out at this point.
She was what, to Bita?
She was calling Bita out.
Okay.
So then she appeared on Bita's again and they had a bit of a thing.
And that's where it is.
The ex-girlfriend is never gonna like the ex-girlfriend.
And why is he poking around the ex-girlfriend anyway?
I think he's trying to triangulate
and doing narcissistic stuff,
but there are narcissists probably too.
Who's triangulating, sorry?
Carl, Carl's trying to like.
Oh, Carl is.
Yeah, he's bringing his new girlfriend
around his old girlfriend.
I mean, what is that about?
Is that you're not supposed to really do that?
Where's the wig?
I think I was getting a little bit too itchy.
I don't know.
So interesting. That's an interesting little twist. I don't know where it stands right now
Last I heard there was talk of Mimi wanting to actually meet up with beta to hash it out
So I don't know what's gonna happen
When you see like I'm in love with her, like she's a powerful love, like I've never even seen her like
outside of like a dark shadow, so I don't know, obviously I don't know if it looks like everybody,
every time I show the AI, I do it for a few months or two is bad, you know, instead of like, oh,
they don't recognize it, excuse me, that's why this image of her of my mind, that's like a fake image,
so if I ever met her, I'd probably be like, my gosh, that's so different, like, I'm gonna probably,
and then it's because I've only seen her in like the shadows, like, I saw her, she was on camera,
but she was like, dark shadows, and you could just see kind of her legs crossed,
I don't know exactly what you're saying because I can barely hear you and I heard something about
Like on the camera and she's like she's sitting in like dark kind of like the shadows who did
Beta and so yeah up here. She looks like how do I so that make me in love with an idea now
I'd make it really pathetic even though like, you know, I did I did like you know
Kind of pretend I don't get it. So she she appeared on camera one day in Dark Shadows
Yeah, yeah, and that means what?
No, that's all that's all that's the only time I've seen her on camera. Oh
Yeah, okay
So I really don't know. She looks like I'm saying I just like I did so how can I be in love with her?
What actually could be different than my image of her because the picture I made of her everyone says oh that
You're there. I mean you can still fall in love with someone someone's character, right? Someone's personality
Say and you're kind of like filling in the rest yourself with your own imagination
No, they said that yeah, they said that isn't like be that that looks like you know, you just cook the fetus
I look like I just googled, you know person woman with curly hair and a big nose
I thought I didn't use I like I got the AI after I got I got her picture off the trip kick video
And then I put in the AI and so it kind of
that looks like her. That's wow, in my mind that's how I see her. Yeah? But I heard she's
like real skinny. I've seen her actually she is real skinny. I always picture her like you know
a little overweight but now she's real skinny. Hey loser. I don't know I don't see her like that
but I mean I've seen her. I see her. Here she goes, that's goes. Yeah.
But I see beat as a which called the avatar, right? So I kind of go by that. Yeah, you're right
I haven't really seen her myself
Right yeah, but these are cartoons many people by this stuff
What it's wrong. No, I don't
You're saying look at the middle one. It's skinny and it's like, yeah, okay, but that doesn't mean that that that's would be the looks like
Try I mean
I thought that was the most close system of what I thought in my mind
But it's like yeah, like I think for example, like if this was one of my try
Okay, well, I don't you know, I don't know. Yeah, it was like here. This one this one was one of them
How does this one look?
Oh, sure. Yeah, I don't think she really likes being portrayed by AI like
She looks more like that
No, I mean, I guess I can see a little bit of the nose
Even doesn't even look like her at all. No, I don't think so me maybe just the nose
But it could be that it's just a nice clip of friendship here. How about that one? No, not at all
That looks like I'm so leaving moon fry. Anyways, I don't want to rate the AI images of beta
I mean, I don't think she likes them
Right, I don't I don't like what she says about me and I don't like how she treats me either
I end as they go and I don't like how she talks about me on her show and
She won't stop it. She's been mean about it and she talks in code and stuff like that and everyone talks in code
What she talks in code
Even the biscuit thing is some stupid stupid uh code. I think it means like you know
Watching if she gets a bunch of guys together they'll drink off on a biscuit and the last one to come pizza
I don't think so man. I think both of you use this biscuit thing just to spite each other
She uses she plays it up
Because she knows it bothers you and you don't like it because you know that that she enjoys it that it's a joke
That she enjoyed yourself a biscuit song, so it's all good. I have a beautiful song and I make good biscuits
She's she's not only saying I'm a bad terror reader, but she's saying I'm a bad biscuit maker and I'm afraid of biscuit
She's not a biscuit attack when I picked up a KFC box
I couldn't admit there's a there's a image of me picking up a KFC box looking frightened
They got you you guys have both taken shots at each other man both of these I
Haven't said anything about the stuff you guys
Did you want but then she's mean about me to me and then she's like she's like
You you've been kind of
Like I actually had like little piece of either like
Has not been like a friend to me at all like a furlough like all these months and stuff like that
And then it's like so I try to like just like get it to like a
These like cordial level as a content creator and it's like so I get at least like, you know, maybe like be able to like
Help if I know things that I could you know with people but it's like at the same time not trying to get involved in people
And then it's like all of a sudden it's like
No, everyone hates me and it's like
Right like it's not just suddenly everybody hates you. Usually something has happened, right?
It hasn't just come out of the blue
Now she might as well she might as well she thinks be this a mastermind person
She might as well like you know team up with beta and like you know figure out how to like who who you know
Who's the third person you mentioned there? Alex and beta. Okay, Alex. All right. I just so wasn't sure
Probably in time they will be okay talking to each other
I don't rule it out.
I know, but then it's like, then they'll be friends
and it's like, and I'll be just like, you know,
just like jerk that they can both say,
oh my God, you think you're a terrible person?
And I was like, I didn't like try to like,
hurt anybody or like do anything wrong.
It's like, I just was like,
just here, I don't know.
I don't think I was like bad
or like sad or something like that.
Like people are always like kind of like,
like I'm like, I'm always feel like I'm like getting punished
or something like that or like getting like, you know,
Kind of the people are too hard on me, but maybe if they had to serve it, I guess
So it's very fitting everyone does it and much
So I can you quickly translate binary
Binary like what does it mean? Yeah, like can you quickly do it open code or something on there?
Yeah, I don't know someone just gave me a message and chat in binary
Oh, well, translate, I don't know how to open it, really.
I'm not that smart, you know what I'm saying?
Never mind.
I'm trying to learn code, but it's like,
I actually, with the website, I'm doing the most code
I've ever done, but at the same time, I'm not a coder.
I'm OK with code.
Like, I'm pretty un-intermediate,
so I can help you out if you have some questions,
but it depends what it is.
Let's go to my website and look at it right now and tell me like a lot of it's not working
But this tell me do you think I can like I can't even work out every day
I have a certain level of it
It's been a psyche first or
Give me one second, you know, I'm still working on this
Binary thing. Oh, it's fine. It's fine. It's someone translate the binary thing. It's it like zeros and ones
Blame site chat. I mean nuts like blame blame time chat
Yeah, the only way I can translate it at the moment is by squishing it all together and then it just gives me a gigantic number
Which is like in the trillions or something
You're too smart for us time just got to tell me what it is man
Okay, sorry psych. What was the what was the website say psycheverse.org?
But it's like silly
I didn't mean wrong time I didn't even take a guess I
Just said I don't know you got to tell me man
psycheverse.com
That or
Okay, what about it? Sorry Alex, I think you know the start of something but it's like I just want to see like
I just want to see how how you think it looks. It's just it seems fine. It seems pretty
a generic as far as modern sites go nothing to generic okay it's not terrible no no i mean it's it's got
the modern style and it's got the modern layout that that's what i mean with
genetic generic i don't mean it in a bad way just bootstrapping the whole thing and so it's yeah
yeah exactly it's not appropriate it's like right at the beginning i have so much i'm going to put
So is everything everything's activated like as far as all the links all buttons and everything are working
I have to like, you know go into like a couple of services like stripe and mail chip and stuff like that
I get them like make sure that all the settings are right. I think they should be easily integrated, but yeah
Hang on no, no Canada dry not a web dev, but I know some coding and I know a little bit of
Does it mean that I can actually work on a study a little bit? Oh, it's a little 23 so I could maybe worse
Shut up Alex. Oh my god. I told you that information if it got out I would be I
Would be chided with it in a childish way and you're the first one to do it the one that I was even telling that it was gonna happen
I mean just ridiculous. Holy crap
Failed it in life
So Alex tell me about your home where you're where you're taking care of your elderly
Family and not leaving them out in the out in the street or out in the cold. Tell me about that
You just want to criticize I know that's what I thought
What site
No, he's now turned against me remember when he was on panel and he said that that it's a good
That's that's the the way to do things to take care of your elderly family in that and to not kick him to the curb
Well now he's in Chad and he's like calling me a loser and all that shit because I live with my mom and my uncle
And my brother right now is has moved in too because he just split with his wife
Okay, is that okay for you Alex or does that also make me a loser fucking idiot? Oh shit
What's that psych
So what are you up to tonight?
Like when I said I could give you a hand I meant like I could help you out and let you know of things with coding that you might need to do
Or what initially I know I don't know like as far as what you want to do with the website. I'm not really a web
Web developers, so I don't know a whole lot about it
I work better with Python.
And it's inspired by IPQ, but I wanted, like, you know,
I wanted to be like a directory where all the live streamers,
when they're on, they'll show who's on,
and then there's going to be a room where like whoever's,
like, on, who's the technical top on the list or whatever
will be playing whenever they're live and stuff,
and like that.
And so, and then people can be introduced to,
like, people, the panellists, or like, you know,
just once you meet something.
Bay.
Oh, my God.
I know what you mean by Python.
That's not what I mean.
Um, no, but I am more of a Python coder and not not so much back end in front end
Like I really don't do much
Anyone else want to jump up? I just was really coming up to let him know what was
Well apparently he was with this girl while he was
Not hitting up, but you know come calling for beta recently lately
So he was apparently with that girl while he was over in beat as saying all in
Sending her chat messages and all are sending her text messages and all that proclaiming his, you know
I just don't understand unless he's like trying to cause trouble, but I'm not jealous of him or I think he's like
Or magical or whatever
Alex do you know what failed to launch what failure to launch is?
Didn't I tell you I lived on my own since I was 20?
I was married
Failure to launch like seriously dude you're
And you're really reaching it
You really want to get to me
Yeah, what we good
Back where I started in my own home. Yes. Thank you, Alex. That's very brilliant
Golden wings glowed in the candlelight
Crowds came running just to see the flame
But envy was the price of fame
And now he stands where the echoes fall
With tarot in hand hearing every call
From praise to venom in the same breath said
But the fire in his eyes burns gold